Guide to the University Archives photograph collection, 1861-ongoing UA.01.15.0009
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Activities Series, 44 Boxes, approx. 22,000 items
  - Athletics
    - Baseball, to 1924 [General], See also Trinity College Collection (Box 37)
    - Baseball, 1924- [General] (Box 37)
    - Baseball (Box 37)
    - Baseball, 1968 (Box 37)
    - Baseball, 1970s (Box 37)
    - Baseball, 1980s (Box 37)
    - Baseball, 1980s [Alumni Games] (Box 38)
    - Baseball, 1980 [Pictures] (Box 38)
    - Baseball, 1980s [Team Photos] (Box 38)
    - Baseball, 1987 (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1906 [Trinity College] (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1908-1909 [Trinity College] (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1909-1910 [Trinity College] (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1920s (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1930s (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1930 (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1940 [First Game, Indoor Stadium] (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1940-1946 (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1948-1949 (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1949-1950 (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1951-1960 [Including First Integrated Game in Cameron] (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1960s (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1960-1961 (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1961-1962 (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1962-1963 (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1964 [NCAA Championship Game, Duke-UCLA] (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1966 (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1967 [Cheerleaders, stands] (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1968 (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1968 [ACC -Duke - NC State ] (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1969 [Blue-White Basketball Game] (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1969-1970 [Managers] (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1970s (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1971? (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1972-1973 (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1973-1974 (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1974 or 1975 (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1977-1978 (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1979-1980 (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1980s (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1987-1988 (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1988-1989 (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1990- (Box 38)
    - Basketball [Basketball Clinic] (Box 38)
    - Basketball [Miscellaneous and n.d.] (Box 38)
    - Basketball [Women's] (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1990s [Women's] (Box 38)
    - Basketball, 1986 [Kryzewskiville] (Box 39)
    - Boxing (Box 39)
    - Cross Country [See also Track] (Box 39)
    - Crowos [Including Cameron Crazies] (missing?) (Box 39)
    - Fencing, 2 folders (Box 39)
    - Fencing, 1966 [NCAA] (Box 39)
    - Fencing, 1972 (Box 39)
    - Field Hockey, Women, 1974 (Box 39)
    - Football, 1892-1896 [Trinity College] (Box 39)
    - Football, 1891 [Trinity College] (Box 39)
    - Football, 1893 [Trinity College] (Box 39)
    - Football, 1900 [Trinity College] (Box 39)
    - Football, 1920s (Box 39)
    - Football, 1921-1927 [Trinity College] (Box 39)
    - Football, 1929 [First Game in New Stadium (Wade Stadium)] (Box 39)
    - Football, 1930s (Box 39)
    - Football, 1938 [Iron Dukes] (Box 39)
    - Football, 1939 [Rose Bowl Collection, Game Photos] (Box 39)
    - Football, 1939 [Rose Bowl, Crowd Scenes, Publicity Shots] (Box 39)
    - Football, 1939 [Rose Bowl, Parade] (Box 39)
    - Football, 1939 [Rose Bowl, Train Trip] (Box 40)
    - Football, 1939 [Rose Bowl, Train Trip, Parade, MGM Studios, etc], 2 folders (Box 40)
    - Football, 1939 [Rose Bowl, Game Only] (Box 40)
    - Football, 1939 [Rose Bowl, Inkjet Prints from A2002-21] (Box 40)
    - Football, 1942 [Rose Bowl, Aerial Views] (Box 40)
    - Football, 1942 [Rose Bowl, Artifacts and News Coverage] (Box 40)
    - Football, 1942 [Rose Bowl, Crowd Shots] (Box 40)
    - Football, 1942 [Rose Bowl, Game Action and Bench] (Box 40)
    - Football, 1942 [Rose Bowl, Pre-Game Activities] (Box 40)
    - Football, 1942 [Rose Bowl, Teams] (Box 40)
    - Football, 1940s (Box 41)
    - Football, 1940s [Individual Players] (Box 41)
    - Football, 1945 [Sugar Bowl] (Box 41)
    - Football, 1948-1949 [Individual Players] (Box 41)
    - Football, 1950s [Individual Players] (Box 41)
    - Football, 1950s [Team Photos, Actions Shots] (Box 41)
    - Football, 1955 [Orange Bowl] (Box 41)
    - Football, 1958 [Orange Bowl] (Box 41)
    - Football, 1960s [Individual Players] (Box 41)
    - Football, 1960s [Team Photos, Action Shots, Elvis Presley] (Box 41)
    - Football, 1961 [Cotton Bowl] (Box 41)
    - Football, 1970s (Box 42)
    - Football, 1970s [Individual Players] (Box 42)
    - Football, 1970s [Specific Games] (Box 42)
    - Football, 1970 [Practice] (Box 42)
    - Football, 1971 [Team at Airport] (Box 42)
    - Football, 1972 [Press Day] (Box 42)
    - Football, 1973 [Press Day] (Box 42)
    - Football, 1973 [Trainers] (Box 42)
    - Football, 1980s (Box 42)
    - Football, 1987 [Trading Cards] (Box 42)
    - Football, 1990s (Box 42)
    - Football, 1935-1970s [Reunion Teams] (Box 42)
    - Football, undated (Box 42)
    - Golf, Men's (Box 42)
    - Golf, Women's (Box 42)
    - Gymnastics (Box 42)
    - Intramurals (Box 42)
    - Lacrosse, Men's (Box 42)
    - Physical Education, Trinity College, See also Oversize Photos (Box 42)
    - Soccer, 1972-1976 (Box 43)
    - Soccer, 1978-1983 (Box 43)
    - Soccer (men's) (Box 43)
    - Soccer (women's) (Box 43)
    - Sports Information (Box 43)
    - Staff, Football Coaches (Box 43)
    - Swimming (men's) (Box 43)
    - Swimming (women's) (Box 43)
    - Tennis, 1915 [Trinity College] (Box 43)
    - Tennis (men's) (Box 43)
    - Tennis (women's) (Box 43)
    - Track (men's) (Box 43)
    - Track (women's) (Box 43)
    - Volleyball (women) (Box 43)
    - Wrestling (Box 43)
  - Band Leaders (Box 43)
  - Banquet in the Inn, c. 1900 (Box 44)
  - Bands and Musical Groups (Box 44)
  - Barbershop (Box 44)
  - Beauty Contest Winners (Box 44)
  - Beta Lambda of Sigma Chi, circa 1925; 1947; undated 1925 (Box 127)
    Includes a list of the names of the individuals in the image on back of matting. Both copies of the undated print also contain lists of individuals on the back of matting, but note one list contains more names.
  - Beta Omega Sigma (Box 44)
  - Beta Phi Zeta, 1972 (Box 44)
  - Big Bands (Box 44)
  - Biology - Class Trip, 1899 (Box 44)
  - Black Studies (Box 44)
  - Blood Donors (Box 44)
  - Blue Devil, See also Homecomings, Cheerleaders (Box 44)
  - BOG Living Group (Box 44)
  - Bonfires, See also Pep Rally (Box 44)
  - Botany Department (Box 44)
  - Botany Department, 1949-1955 (Box 44)
  - Boy Scout Camporee (Box 44)
  - Brooks Literary Society (Box 44)
  - Brown House (Box 44)
  - Bus Boycott, See also Student Life 1950s (Box 44)
  - Buses (Box 44)
  - Cable 13 TV, 1978 (Box 44)
  - Campaign for Duke, 2004 (Box 44)
  - Campus Club (Box 44)
  - Celebrity Classic (Box 44)
  - Centennial Celebration, 1938-1939 [Includes Doris Duke] (Box 44)
  - Centennial Celebration (Box 44)
  - Cerebral Palsy (Hospital), 1968 (Box 45)
  - Chancel Singers (Box 45)
  - Chanticleer (Box 45)
  - Chanticleer, 1964-1968 (Box 45)
  - Chapel Choir (Box 45)
  - Cheerleaders, pre-1990, 2 folders (Box 45)
  - Cheerleaders, 1971-1972 (Box 45)
  - Chemistry Department (Box 45)
  - Chemistry Brochure, 1968 (Box 45)
  - Chemistry, 1968 (Box 45)
  - Chemistry, 1971 [Carbide Summer Fellows] (Box 45)
  - Chemistry, 1970 [Walk With Students] (Box 45)
  - Chemistry, 1973 [Brochure] (Box 45)
  - Chemistry, 1972 (Box 45)
  - Chemistry, 1971 [Faculty Labs, Etc.] (Box 45)
  - Chemistry, 1973 [Students] (Box 45)
  - Chemistry, 1971 [Students for EWW] (Box 45)
  - Child Guidance Clinic (Box 45)
  - China Trip, 1975 (Box 45)
  - Chorale (Box 45)
  - Christmas Pageant (Box 45)
  - Chronicle (Box 45)
  - Ciompi Quartet (Box 46)
  - Commencements General #2 (Box 46)
  - Class Agent's Day (Box 46)
  - Classes / Reunions
    - 1891-1893 (Box 46)
    - 1906 [Album] (Box 46)
    - 1909 [Album] (Box 46)
    - 1894 (Box 46)
    - 1895 (Box 46)
    - 1896 [Individual Portraits] (Box 46)
    - 1896 (Box 46)
    - 1896, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - 1899 (Box 47)
    - 1902 (Box 47)
    - 1903 (Box 47)
    - 1904 (Box 47)
    - 1905 (Box 47)
    - 1906 [Individuals] (Box 47)
    - 1906 [Albums] (Box 47)
    - 1906 (Box 47)
    - 1907 [Album, Includes Mary Lillian Duke] (Box 47)
    - 1907 (Box 47)
    - 1908 [Album] (Box 48)
    - 1908 (Box 48)
    - 1909 [Album] (Box 48)
    - 1909 [Individual Photos] (Box 48)
    - 1909 [See also MC 5] (Box 48)
    - 1910 (Box 48)
    - 1911 [Individuals] (Box 48)
    - 1911 [Classes] (Box 48)
    - 1912 (Box 48)
    - 1913 (Box 48)
    - 1916 (Box 48)
    - 1917 (Box 48)
    - 1918 (Box 48)
    - 1920 (Box 48)
    - 1921 (Box 48)
    - 1922 (Box 48)
    - 1923 (Box 48)
    - 1925 (Box 48)
    - 1926 (Box 48)
    - 1927 (Box 49)
    - 1929 (Box 49)
    - 1930 (Box 49)
    - 1931 (Box 49)
    - 1932 (Box 49)
    - 1934 (Box 49)
    - 1935 (Box 49)
    - 1936 (Box 49)
    - 1937 (Box 49)
    - 1939 (Box 49)
    - 1939 [Electrical Engineering] (Box 49)
    - 1942 (Box 49)
    - 1943 (Box 49)
    - 1944 (Box 49)
    - 1945 (Box 49)
    - 1946 (Box 49)
    - 1947 (Box 49)
    - 1948 (Box 49)
    - 1951 (Box 49)
    - 1952 (Box 49)
    - 1954 (Box 49)
    - 1955 (Box 49)
    - 1958 (Box 49)
    - 1961 (Box 49)
    - 1962 (Box 49)
    - 1963 (Box 49)
    - 1964 (Box 49)
    - 1967 [First Black Undergraduates, 1963-64] (Box 49)
    - 1968 (Box 49)
    - 1969 (Box 49)
    - 1970 (Box 49)
    - 1971 (Box 49)
    - 1972 (Box 49)
    - 1973 (Box 49)
    - 1981 (Box 49)
    - 1982 (Box 49)
    - 1984 (Box 49)
    - 2001 (Box 49)
    - 2010 (Box 49)
  - Cleland House (Living Group) (Box 49)
  - College Bowl Teams [See also Wetherby Papers, Debate] (Box 49)
  - Collegium Musicum (Box 49)
  - Commencement
    - 1885, 1888, 1889, 1891 (Box 49)
    - 1892 (Box 49)
    - 1894 (Box 49)
    - 1896 (Box 49)
    - 1910-1919 (Box 49)
    - 1920s (Box 50)
    - 1930 (East Campus) (Box 50)
    - 1931 (Box 50)
    - 1932 (Box 50)
    - 1933 (Box 50)
    - 1934, 1935 (Box 50)
    - 1936 (Box 50)
    - 1937 (Box 50)
    - 1938 (Box 50)
    - 1939 (Box 50)
    - 1940 (Box 50)
    - 1941 (Box 50)
    - 1942 (Box 50)
    - 1946 (Box 50)
    - 1947 (Box 50)
    - 1948 (Box 50)
    - 1949 (Box 50)
    - 1950 (Box 50)
    - 1951 (Box 50)
    - 1952 (Box 50)
    - 1953 (Box 50)
    - 1954 (Box 51)
    - 1955 (Box 51)
    - 1956 (Box 51)
    - 1958 (Box 51)
    - 1959 (Box 51)
    - 1960 (Box 51)
    - 1961 (Box 51)
    - 1962 (Box 51)
    - 1963 (Box 51)
    - 1964 (Box 51)
    - 1965 (Box 51)
    - 1966 (Box 51)
    - 1967 (Box 51)
    - 1967 [Hippocratic Oath, Medical] (Box 51)
    - 1968, 2 folders (Box 51)
    - 1968 (Box 52)
    - 1969 (Box 52)
    - 1970 (Box 52)
    - 1970 [Contact Prints and Negative Strips] (Box 52)
    - 1970 (Box 52)
    - 1971 (Box 52)
    - 1972 (Box 52)
    - 1973 (Box 53)
    - 1974 (Box 53)
    - 1975 (Box 53)
    - 1976 (Box 53)
    - 1977 (Box 53)
    - 1979 [Includes Go To Hell Carolina Banner] (Box 53)
    - 1980 (Box 53)
    - 1981 (Box 53)
    - 1982 (Box 53)
    - 1984 (Box 53)
    - 1985 (Box 53)
    - 1986 (Box 53)
    - 1987 (Box 53)
    - 1989 (Box 53)
    - 1995 (Box 53)
  - Commencements, General (Box 53)
  - Commencement Programs (Box 53)
  - Commonwealth Studies (Box 53)
  - Community Sing (Box 53)
  - Computers (Box 53)
  - Concert Band [See also Pep Band, DUMB] (Box 53)
  - Convocation, Christian and Pastor's School (Box 53)
  - Convocation 1964 (Box 54)
  - Convocation 1968 (Box 54)
  - Dad's Day (Box 54)
  - Dance, Modern (Box 54)
  - Dead Sea Scrolls, 1950? (Box 54)
  - Delta Delta Delta (Box 54)
  - Debating Team (Box 54)
  - Debate Team - College Bowl Team (Box 54)
  - Debate Team, 1898 [Trinity v. Wake Forest] (Box 54)
  - Delta Phi Rho Alpha [Women's Athletic Society] (Box 54)
  - Delta Theta Phi (Box 54)
  - Demonstrations and Protests [Includes Woolworth Lunch Counter] (Box 54)
  - Demonstrations
    - Allen Building Sit-In, 1967 (Box 54)
    - The Vigil, 1968 [Contact Prints and Negatives] (Box 54)
    - The Vigil, 1968 [Prints, Slides] (Box 54)
    - The Vigil, 1968 [Negatives, Contact Prints, Unmatched] (Box 54)
    - The Vigil, 1968 [Contact Prints and Negatives, 2.25"] (Box 54)
    - Dow Chemical, 1968 (Box 54)
    - Allen Building, 1968 (Box 54)
    - Allen Building, 1969 (Box 54)
    - ROTC Demonstration, 1969 (Box 54)
    - May 1970 Demonstrations, 1970 (Box 54)
    - 1980s Demonstrations, 1981, 1987, 1989 [Take Back the Night, Women's Rights, Nixon Library] (Box 54)
    - Duke South African Coalition Divestment, 1985, 1986 (Box 54)
    - Amnesty International, 1990s (Box 54)
    - Allen Building Takeover, 1969 (Transferred from School of Law Records, A. Kenneth Pye Series) (Box 54)
  - University Development (Box 55)
  - Dietetics, School of (Box 55)
  - Dining Halls, Interior, 1967 (Box 55)
  - Dining Halls, Dining Rooms (Box 55)
  - Dining Hall Service for Institutions Magazine, 1974 (Box 55)
  - Dining Halls, Kitchens and Staff (Box 55)
  - Diplomas (Box 55)
  - Divinity School, 3 folders (Box 55)
  - Divinity School [Class of 1936] (Box 55)
  - Divinity School [Class of 1981] (Box 55)
  - Divinity School [Class of 1998] (Box 55)
  - Divinity School [Class of 2002] (Box 55)
  - Divinity School [Faculty, Group Photos] (Box 55)
  - Drama Program (Box 55)
  - Drum Majorettes (Box 55)
  - Duke Ambassadors (Band) [See also Duke Collegians] (Box 55)
  - Duke Baseball team/Seeman Printery (?), circa 1925; undated 1925 (Box 127)
    Print, de-matted, of baseball team with image of what may be Seeman Printery adhered to back. Name of team members on back of matting.
  - Duke Card (Box 56)
  - Duke Collegians (Johnny Long Band) [See also Duke Ambassadors] (Box 56)
  - Duke Endowment (Box 56)
  - Duke Fellows in Communication, 1974 (Box 56)
  - Duke Players #1, 2 folders (Box 56)
  - Duke Players #2 (Box 56)
  - Duke Players #3, 1971 [Alumni Register, 1971] (Box 56)
  - Duke Players #4, 1985 ["Past Grand Knight"] (Box 56)
  - Duke Players #5, 1985 ["To Kill a Mockingbird"] (Box 56)
  - Duke Players #6, 1968 ["A Streetcar Named Desire"] (Box 56)
  - Duke Players #7, 1986 ["Romeo and Juliet"] (Box 56)
  - Duke Players #8A (Box 56)
  - Duke Players #8B (Box 56)
  - Duke Players #9 (Box 56)
  - Duke Players #10 (Box 57)
  - Duke Players #11 (Box 57)
  - Duke Players #12 (Box 57)
  - Duke Recycles (Box 57)
  - Duke Symphony Orchestra [See also Allan Bone] (Box 57)
  - Duke University Marching Band and Trinity Band 1915, 2 folders (Box 57)
  - Duke University Press (Box 57)
  - Dukes and Duchesses (Box 57)
  - Economics Department (Box 57)
  - Edgemont Community Center (Box 57)
  - Education Conference (Cartwright), 1968 (Box 57)
  - Education Department (Box 58)
  - Education Department [School Law Conferences] (Box 58)
  - Education Leadership Summit, 2002 (Box 58)
  - Engineering [Class Photos] (Box 58)
  - Engineering, 1930-1933 [Ralph T. Mathews Photograph Collection] (Box 58)
  - Engineering [Engineers' Shows] (Box 58)
  - Engineering [Faculty, Group Photographs] (Box 58)
  - Engineering [Group Photos], 2 folders (Box 58)
  - Engineering, School of (Box 59)
    - Labs and Field Trips, 1936-1938 (Box 59)
    - Labs and Classes I (Box 59)
    - Labs and Classes II, 2 folders (Box 59)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 59)
    - Reunions (Box 59)
    - Societies and Clubs (Box 59)
    - Class of 1942 (Box 59)
    - Seniors, Mechanical Engineering, 1942 (Box 59)
    - Engineering Brochure, 1966 (Box 59)
    - NASA Story, 1966 (Box 59)
    - Engineering Feature, 1967 (Box 59)
    - E.A. Link Feature, 1968 [Visitor to Engineering] (Box 59)
    - Stress Feature, 1968 (Box 59)
    - Civil Engineering Brochure, 1971 (Box 59)
    - Electrical Engineering, 1955-1961 [Harry Owen Photos, Acc. No. 85-93], 2 folders (Box 59)
    - Electrical Engineering [Harry Owen Photos] (Box 60)
    - Electrical Engineering Class of 1939 [See: Otto Meier, Jr. (Addition)] (Box 60)
    - Electrical Engineering Miscellaneous [See: Otto Meier, Jr. (Addition)] (Box 60)
    - Engineering Surveyors, 1973 (Box 60)
  - English Department (Box 60)
  - Episcopal Youth (Box 60)
  - Faculty - Trinity College (Box 60)
  - Faculty - Trinity College, 1900-1901 [Individual Photos] (Box 60)
  - Faculty Baseball Games, 1950s (Box 60)
  - Faculty Club (Box 60)
  - Faculty, Children of [Trinity College] (Box 60)
  - Faculty and Staff [General and Group] (Box 60)
  - Faculty Plays (Box 60)
  - Faculty Meeting (Box 60)
  - Fifth Decade Leaders (Box 60)
  - First Ph.D.'s (Box 60)
  - First State Award [Fisher Body Craftsman's Guild] (Box 60)
  - Flag Raising (Box 60)
  - Flying Club (Box 60)
  - Folk Festival, 1972 (Box 60)
  - Foreign Students [See also Cheasty, Denise ] (Box 61)
  - Foreign Visitors (Box 61)
  - School of Forestry and Environmental Science [Activities] (Box 61)
  - Forestry
    - to 1950 (Box 61)
    - 1950-1969 (Box 61)
    - Contact Sheets and Negatives, 1968-1970 (Box 61)
    - 1970-, 2 folders (Box 61)
    - Brochure, 1972 (Box 61)
    - Forestry Club (Environmental Management Club) (Box 61)
    - Faculty [Individuals] (Box 61)
    - Forestry, Faculty [Groups] (Box 62)
    - Forestry, Field Day, 1984 (Box 62)
  - Forum Club [Trinity College] (Box 62)
  - Founder's Day (Box 62)
  - Founder's Day 1956, 1956 [See also Doris Duke] (Box 62)
  - Founder's Society (Box 62)
  - Fraternities, General (Box 62)
  - Fraternities, Black (Box 62)
  - Freshman Arrivals (Move-in Day)
    - to 1959 (Box 62)
    - 1960- (Box 62)
    - 1967 (Box 62)
    - 1969 (Box 62)
    - 1970 (Box 62)
    - 1972 (Box 62)
    - 1973 (Box 62)
    - 1985 (Box 62)
    - Women's College Opening (Box 62)
  - Freshmen Traditions [Dinks and Bows] (Box 62)
  - Freshmen Week, to 1959, 2 folders (Box 62)
  - Friends of Duke University Library (Box 63)
  - Friends of the Library - Book Collector's Award (Box 63)
  - Fubar - Homecoming, 1979 (Box 63)
  - Fulbright Scholars (Box 63)
  - Geology - Fossil of Worm (Box 63)
  - Germanic Languages, Department of (Box 63)
  - Gilbert-Addoms Residents (Group) (Box 63)
  - Glee Club, Men's [Trinity College] (Box 63)
  - Glee Club, Men's #1 (Box 63)
  - Glee Club, Men's #2 (Box 63)
  - Glee Club (Joint) [Includes Chapel Choir] (Box 63)
  - Glee Club, Women's (Box 63)
  - Goon Day (Box 63)
  - Gothic Bookshop (Box 63)
  - Graduate School Development Advisory Committee (Box 63)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences (Box 63)
  - Grateful Dead, 1982 (Box 63)
  - Heart Fund (Box 63)
  - Hiking Club, Women's, 1924 [Trinity College] (Box 63)
  - Higher Education Conference, 1968 [Quail Roost] (Box 63)
  - History Department (Box 63)
  - Holiday Tree Lighting (Box 63)
  - Homecoming
    - 1930s (Box 63)
    - 1935 [Blue Devil, Steam Engine] (Box 63)
    - 1940s (Box 63)
    - 1950s (Box 63)
    - 1960s-1970s [Loose Negatives] (Box 63)
    - Homecoming 1960s (Box 64)
    - Homecoming 1970s (Box 64)
    - Homecoming, n.d. (Box 64)
  - Hoof 'n' Horn
    - General, 2 folders (Box 64)
    - "You're a Good Man, Charlie Brown", 1979 (Box 64)
    - "A Little Night Music", 1975 (Box 64)
    - "Grease", 1981 (Box 64)
    - "West Side Story", 1982 (Box 64)
    - "Music Man", 1983 (Box 64)
    - "Anything Goes", 1986 (Box 64)
  - House P (Living Group) (Box 64)
  - Human Resources, Department of (Box 64)
  - Hurricane Hazel Cleanup (Box 64)
  - Hyperbaric Chamber (Box 64)
  - Information Services, Office of (Box 64)
  - International Studies, International House (Box 64)
  - Iota Gamma Pi (Box 64)
  - "Joe College" Weekend (Box 64)
  - Kappa Alpha Order (Box 65)
  - Kappa Delta (Box 65)
  - Kappa Sigma (Box 65)
  - Kiddie College, c. 1957 (Box 65)
  - Law School
    - Trinity College (Box 65)
    - 1920s (Box 65)
    - 1930s (Box 65)
    - 1930s-1959, 2 folders (Box 65)
    - 1960s-1970s (Box 65)
    - Class Pictures (Box 65)
    - Faculty (Box 65)
    - Brochures and Bulletins (Box 65)
    - Legal Aid Clinic (Box 65)
    - Library (Box 65)
  - League of Women Voters (Box 65)
  - Library, West Campus
    - Exhibits (Box 65)
    - Perkins Dedication, 1970 (Box 65)
    - Personnel and Guests/Visitors (Box 65)
    - Rare Book Room Dedication, 1949-1950 (Box 65)
  - Library Trent - Marine Lab #4 (Box 66)
    - Library, Trent Collection (Box 66)
    - Library, West Campus, 1979 [Three Millionth Book Ceremony] (Box 66)
    - Library (Box 66)
    - Lilly Endowment Conference (Box 66)
    - Literary Arts Societies (Box 66)
    - LM Dignitaries Dinner, 1974 (Box 66)
    - Mace and Chain of Duke University (Box 66)
    - Madrigal Singers (Box 66)
    - Marine Laboratory #1 (Box 66)
    - Marine Laboratory #2 (Box 66)
    - Marine Laboratory #3 (Box 66)
    - Marine Laboratory #4 (Box 66)
  - Marine Laboratory #5 (Box 67)
  - Marine Laboratory - Vessels - Eastward (Box 67)
  - Marine Laboratory - Vessels - Other (Box 67)
  - Mary Lou Williams Center for Black Culture (Box 67)
  - Mathematics Department (Box 67)
  - Mathematics Institute, 1940s (Box 67)
  - Mathematics Institute, 1950s (Box 67)
  - May Day Celebration (Box 67)
  - May Day, 2 folders (Box 67)
  - Medical Center - Aging and Human Development [See also Gerontology] (Box 67)
  - Medical Center - Alumni and Ivy Planting, 1968 (Box 67)
  - Medical Center - Art Department (Box 67)
  - Medical Center (Box 68)
    - Brochures (Box 68)
    - Catheter Med., 1971 (Box 68)
    - Emergency, 1968 (Box 68)
    - Eye Center (Box 68)
    - General (Box 68)
    - Gerontology (Box 68)
    - Hospital Administration (Box 68)
    - Hospital Auxiliary (Box 68)
    - Intensive Care (Box 68)
    - Laboratories, Blood and Cancer Labs (Box 68)
    - Neurology (Box 68)
    - Patients and Patient Life (Box 68)
    - Pediatrics/Neonatology [Includes Premature Nursery] (Box 68)
    - Physicians (Box 68)
    - Physicians' Assistant Program, 1969 (Box 68)
    - Research (Box 68)
    - Staff, 1930 (Box 68)
    - Students (Box 68)
    - Surgery, Department of (Box 68)
  - Men's Student Government (Box 68)
  - Methodist Church - Methodist School of Missions (Box 68)
  - Methodist Church - Methodist Youth Fellowship (Box 68)
  - Methodist Student Fellowship: Wesley Players (Box 68)
  - Ministerial Associates, 1926 (Box 68)
  - Minority Conference, 1977 (Box 68)
  - Music Department (Box 68)
  - National Council (Box 68)
  - Nearly New Shoppe (Box 68)
  - Nereidian (Box 68)
  - News Service (Box 68)
  - "9019" Society - Trinity College (Box 68)
  - N.C. Folklife Festival (Box 68)
  - N.C. Press Association Dinners [Includes Press Institute] (Box 68)
  - N.C. Regional Medical, 1970 (Box 68)
  - N.C. School of Science and Math (Box 69)
  - Graduate Nurses, Class of 1978 (Box 69)
  - Nursing, School of (Box 69)
  - Nursing School (Box 69)
  - Oak Ridge (Box 69)
  - Octopus Club (Faculty Discussion Group) (Box 69)
  - Old Trinity Club (Secret Society) (Box 69)
  - Omega Phi Psi (Box 69)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa (Men's Honorary) (Box 69)
  - Opening Ceremonies, 1963 (Box 69)
  - Order of the Chair (Box 69)
  - Pep Band (Box 69)
  - Orchestra, Women's [See Bands and Musical Groups] (Box 69)
  - Out of the Blue (Student Singing Group) (Box 69)
  - Outing Club [See also Flying Club] (Box 69)
  - Pan Hellenic Council (Box 69)
  - Parapsychology [See also Rhine, J.B.] (Box 69)
  - Parents' Weekend (Box 69)
  - Parking Facilities - Construction (Box 69)
  - Pastor's School (Box 69)
  - Peer (Campus Humor Magazine) (Box 69)
  - Pep Rally (Box 69)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1920 (Box 69)
  - Phi Delta Theta (Box 69)
  - Phi Kappa Psi (Box 69)
  - Phi Kappa Sigma (Box 69)
  - Philosophy Department (Box 69)
  - Physical Education (Box 69)
  - Physical Education, Women's (Box 69)
  - Physical Education - Women's Archery (Box 70)
  - Physical Therapy (Box 70)
  - Physics Department (Box 70)
  - Pi Beta Phi - Group Pictures, 1983 (Box 70)
  - Pi Kappa Alpha (Box 70)
  - Pi Phi (Box 70)
  - Pitchforks - Student Singing (Box 70)
  - Placement Office (Box 70)
  - Poison Control Center (Box 70)
  - Policy Sciences, Institute of, 1974 (Box 70)
  - Political Science, Department of (Box 70)
  - Posters (Box 70)